andesnetwork.com 2012-12-30

# Andesnetwork.com

### Privacy Policy

* * *

Your privacy is important to Andes Network and we are committed to protecting the privacy of our members. This statement discloses the information practices including what information is gathered and how information is used. 

**Cookies**  
Cookies can be used to provide the user with tailored information from a Web site and improve the user's online experience. A cookie is a part of data that Web site can send to your browser, which may be stored in the user's system. No information that is personally identifiable is linked with our use of cookies. Cookies are not viruses and are unable to harm your computer. 

**Sharing and using personal information**  
All personal information that is collected by Andes Network is intended for internal use only. This includes information such as Contact Name, Address, Email, Tax ID and etc. US publisher's information such as tax ID and etc. may be used so that commissions earned can be reported to the appropriate taxation authorities. None-personally identifiable information such as visited URLs, IP addresses, cookies shown, date/time of visit and etc. is collected from Web users to assist in the proper function of our service as well as the targeting of advertisements from our customers and the reporting of combined data to both advertisers and publishers. Advertisers may implore third-party service providers that collect anonymous user visit information, Andes Network cannot be held responsible for the actions of third parties or their privacy practices as we have no control over the information collected. Andes Network does not sell or purchase Web user information that is personally identifiable. 

**Security**  
We intend to protect your personal information and use every precaution to ensure that all personal information collected is secure such as using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when the information is stored. Web security is monitored on a constant basis, and adheres to strict regulations. 

**Members**  
Members will have access to their personal account information such as billing information, statistical account information, advertisements, etc via username and password. This area is subject to additional security measures and monitoring in order to protect the sensitive information. 

**External links**  
Andes Network Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. Andes Network is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other Web sites. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
We recommend that you periodically review this Privacy Policy, because it may be updated from time to time. In case of change, all changes will be posted on this current page. 

**Contacting Andes Network**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site please contact us.
